Hello English learners.
各位英语学习者，大家好。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And I'm Erica.
我是Erica。
And today we're bringing you our great suspense, scary series.
今天我们要为大家带来精彩的悬疑惊悚系列。
Our thriller.
我们的惊悚剧。
Our thriller, New Guy in Town, part four.
我们的惊悚剧，《小镇新面孔》第四部分。
All right.
好的。
Well, I don't want to give you any hints about what will happen in this dialogue.
嗯，我不想透露这段对话中会发生什么。
Yes, it's totally unexpected.
是的，完全出乎意料。
So let's listen to our dialogue and then we'll come back and talk about some of the great
所以让我们先听对话，然后回来讨论一些精彩的
vocabulary.
词汇。
All right.
好的。
Drag her over here and help me tie her up.
把她拖过来，帮我绑住她。
I can't believe she fell for it.
真不敢相信她上当了。
She is a lot more gullible than I thought.
她比我想象的更容易受骗。
Well, you got to admit my acting was brilliant.
嗯，你得承认我的演技很出色。
Whatever.
随便吧。
I was the one that convinced her to come.
是我说服她来的。
Look, she's waking up.
看，她醒了。
What's going on, Ellen?
怎么回事，Ellen？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
The cat's out of the bag, you witch.
秘密暴露了，你这个女巫。
You can stop pretending now.
你可以别再装了。
Yeah, Lois, we know who you are.
是啊，Lois，我们知道你是谁。
Now we want some answers.
现在我们要你回答一些问题。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这里？
You don't know who you're dealing with.
你不知道你在跟谁打交道。
You can't stop me.
你阻止不了我。
Well, I certainly didn't see that one coming.
嗯，我确实没想到会这样。
I know everyone thought that Armand was a vampire.
我知道大家都以为Armand是吸血鬼。
I know.
我知道。
And now it turns out that they were acting.
结果他们是在演戏。
Yeah, crazy.
是啊，真疯狂。
Crazy, huh?
疯狂，是吧？
Yeah.
是啊。
Strange things happen here on EnglishPod.
在EnglishPod上总是发生奇怪的事。
All right, so why don't we take a look at some of the language that we saw in Language
好的，那我们来看看“语言要点”中的一些语言点。
Takeaway.
语言要点。
Language Takeaway.
Well, we have three words for you here that we heard in the dialogue.
嗯，我们这里有三个在对话中听到的单词。
And the first one, Armand tells Ellen to drag her over here.
第一个，Armand让Ellen把她拖过来。
Right, drag.
对，拖。
Drag.
拖。
So when you drag something or somebody.
所以当你拖某物或某人时。
You pull them across the floor or pull them across the ground.
你把他们在地板上或地面上拉。
Pull them, but you don't actually pick them up, right?
拉他们，但实际上不把他们抱起来，对吧？
No.
不。
Yeah.
对。
Their body is still touching the ground.
他们的身体还接触地面。
Okay, so just imagine if you have a really heavy suitcase, it doesn't have any wheels,
好的，想象一下如果你有一个很重的行李箱，没有轮子，
you got to drag it across the floor.
你得把它拖过地板。
Yeah.
对。
Right?
对吧？
I've been there.
我经历过。
Yeah, it's happened to me too.
是啊，我也遇到过。
Yeah.
对。
So drag.
所以是拖。
All right.
好的。
And then he says, tie her up.
然后他说，绑住她。
Tie her up.
绑住她。
Tie somebody up.
绑住某人。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
So to tie somebody up.
所以绑住某人。
To use rope and put it around a person so that they cannot move.
用绳子绕在一个人身上，让他们不能动。
Right.
对。
So you take rope, you tie a person up.
所以你拿绳子，绑住一个人。
And it's always used like this, right?
而且总是这样用，对吧？
Tie somebody up.
绑住某人。
Yes.
是的。
Tie him up.
绑住他。
Tie that up.
绑住那个。
Yeah.
对。
Okay.
好的。
And our last word.
最后一个词。
I like this one.
我喜欢这个。
Fools.
傻瓜们。
So our singular would be fool.
所以单数是傻瓜。
Yeah, F-O-O-L.
对，F-O-O-L。
So what's a fool?
那傻瓜是什么意思？
Well, a fool is a stupid person.
嗯，傻瓜就是愚蠢的人。
Right.
对。
A person that doesn't know something.
一个不知道某事的人。
Yes.
是的。
Or an ignorant person.
或者无知的人。
All right.
好的。
Well, Lois thinks that Armand and Ellen are fools here.
嗯，Lois认为Armand和Ellen是傻瓜。
Exactly.
没错。
Apparently, she got really angry and managed to escape from the chair or whatever.
显然，她非常生气，设法从椅子上或别的什么东西上逃脱了。
She was tied up, right?
她被绑着，对吧？
Well, the dialogue was a little bit fast.
嗯，对话有点快。
There was a lot of sound effects as well.
还有很多音效。
Yeah.
对。
So let's listen to this dialogue again.
所以让我们再听一遍这段对话。
We're going to slow it down a little bit.
我们会放慢一点速度。
And I'm sure it's going to be a little bit easier to understand.
我相信会更容易理解。
All right.
好的。
Drag her over here and help me tie her up.
把她拖过来，帮我绑住她。
I can't believe she fell for it.
真不敢相信她上当了。
She is a lot more gullible than I thought.
她比我想象的更容易受骗。
Well, you got to admit, my acting was brilliant.
嗯，你得承认我的演技很出色。
Whatever.
随便吧。
I was the one that convinced her to come.
是我说服她来的。
Look, she's waking up.
看，她醒了。
What's going on, Ellen?
怎么回事，Ellen？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
The cat's out of the bag, you witch.
秘密暴露了，你这个女巫。
You can stop pretending now.
你可以别再装了。
Yeah, Lois.
是啊，Lois。
We know who you are.
我们知道你是谁。
Now we want some answers.
现在我们要你回答一些问题。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这里？
Fools!
傻瓜们！
You don't know who you're dealing with.
你不知道你在跟谁打交道。
You can't stop me.
你阻止不了我。
Run!
快跑！
So Marco, I noticed in this dialogue, there's a lot of words and phrases that we can use
所以Marco，我注意到在这段对话中，有很多单词和短语可以用来谈论说谎或愚弄某人。
to talk about lying or fooling somebody.
没错。
Exactly.
有很多关于说谎的语言。
There is a lot of language about lying.
所以让我们在“流利度构建”中看看。
So let's take a look at it in Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
Fluency Builder.
All right.
好的。
So in Fluency Builder today, let's take a look at four phrases.
所以在今天的“流利度构建”中，我们来看四个短语。
The first one, fell for it.
第一个，上当了。
Fell for it.
上当了。
I can't believe she fell for it.
真不敢相信她上当了。
Fell for it.
上当了。
Okay, so it's not that she physically fell, right?
好的，所以不是她身体上摔倒了，对吧？
No, no.
不，不是。
Okay.
好的。
But she believed the lie.
但她相信了谎言。
She believed the lie.
她相信了谎言。
You fell for the lie.
你中了谎言的圈套。
Yeah.
对。
I know that we have some examples so we can understand this phrase, fell for it, a little
我知道我们有一些例子，可以更好地理解这个短语“上当了”。
bit better.
例子一。
Example one.
He might seem like a nice guy, but don't fall for it.
他可能看起来是个好人，但别上当。
He's a jerk.
他是个混蛋。
Example two.
例子二。
I can't believe I fell for your lies.
真不敢相信我中了你的谎言。
Example three.
例子三。
I told my mom I was going to the library and she fell for it.
我告诉我妈我要去图书馆，她信了。
All right.
好的。
Well, that's a lot clearer to me.
嗯，这对我来说清楚多了。
I noticed that we have the preposition it here.
我注意到这里有个介词“它”。
Yeah.
对。
It is at the end and it's referring to the lie.
它在结尾，指的是谎言。
Yes.
是的。
Or the joke or the story.
或者玩笑或故事。
Yeah.
对。
She fell for the story.
她相信了那个故事。
But you wouldn't say she fell for the story.
但你不会说“她相信了那个故事”。
You would say she fell for it.
你会说“她上当了”。
Yeah.
对。
So these three words always, always, always go together.
所以这三个词总是、总是、总是连在一起。
Fell for it.
上当了。
So don't forget the it.
所以别忘了“它”。
Don't forget the it.
别忘了“它”。
Okay.
好的。
Let's take a look at our second word.
我们来看第二个词。
Gullible.
容易受骗的。
So Ellen thinks that Lois was gullible.
所以Ellen认为Lois容易受骗。
Right.
对。
A gullible person.
一个容易受骗的人。
Yeah.
对。
Gullible.
容易受骗的。
A gullible person is somebody that always believes.
一个容易受骗的人就是总是相信别人的人。
Yes.
是的。
They always fall for it.
他们总是上当。
Yeah.
对。
They believe anything you say.
他们相信你说的任何话。
So you were a little bit gullible when you were younger, right?
所以你小时候有点容易受骗，对吧？
Yeah.
对。
That's true.
没错。
You know what?
你知道吗？
My grandmother used to tell me every year she would say, oh, I'm 35.
我奶奶每年都跟我说，哦，我35岁了。
I'm 35.
我35岁了。
And I really believed her until I was about 12 years old.
我一直相信她，直到我大概12岁。
Wow.
哇。
So you were really gullible.
所以你真的很容易受骗。
Really gullible.
真的很天真。
But you're not anymore.
但你现在不了。
No.
不。
I know better.
我懂了。
All right.
好的。
So gullible.
所以容易受骗的。
A gullible person.
一个容易受骗的人。
Okay.
好的。
Now let's look at the next phrase.
现在来看下一个短语。
The cat's out of the bag.
秘密暴露了。
The cat is out of the bag.
Okay.
好的。
So again, it's not literal.
所以同样，这不是字面意思。
It's not like you had a cat in a bag and you let it out.
这不像你把猫放在袋子里然后放出来。
No.
不。
A nice idiom here, meaning the truth is out.
这里有个好习语，意思是真相大白了。
The truth is out.
真相大白了。
We discovered the truth.
我们发现了真相。
Yes.
是的。
So imagine that the cat is the truth.
所以想象猫就是真相。
Right.
对。
And it escaped.
它逃出来了。
Yes.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
So the cat's out of the bag.
所以猫从袋子里出来了。
The truth is out.
真相大白了。
We know the truth now.
我们现在知道真相了。
Yep.
嗯。
Okay.
好的。
So let's look at our last phrase.
那我们来看看最后一个短语。
Pretending.
假装。
So Lois was pretending to be a normal housewife.
所以洛伊斯在假装成一个普通的家庭主妇。
Let's listen to some examples of how we would use pretending.
我们来听一些如何使用“假装”的例子。
Example one.
例子一。
Pretend that you're my boyfriend and he'll go away.
假装你是我男朋友，他就会走开。
Example two.
例子二。
I can't believe Lucy pretended to be sick.
我简直不敢相信露西假装生病。
Example three.
例子三。
You forgot my birthday.
你忘了我的生日。
Don't pretend that everything is okay.
别假装一切都好。
Okay.
好的。
So pretending is acting like you are somebody that you are not.
所以“假装”就是表现得像你不是的那个人。
Yes.
是的。
Or, yeah, it's sort of like acting a lie.
或者，嗯，有点像在演一个谎言。
Okay.
好的。
So for example, on Halloween, everyone dresses up as a monster or Spider-Man or something.
比如，在万圣节，每个人都打扮成怪物或蜘蛛侠之类的。
So everyone pretends to be that character.
所以每个人都假装成那个角色。
Yes.
是的。
But they are not.
但他们并不是。
Yes.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
Pretending.
假装。
Okay.
好的。
So let's listen to her dialogue one more time and then we'll come back and talk some more.
那我们再听一遍她的对话，然后回来再聊。
All right.
好的。
Drag her over here and help me tie her up.
把她拖过来，帮我绑起来。
I can't believe she fell for it.
我真不敢相信她上当了。
She is a lot more gullible than I thought.
她比我想象的容易上当得多。
Well, you got to admit my acting was brilliant.
嗯，你得承认我的演技很棒。
Whatever.
随便吧。
I was the one that convinced her to come.
是我说服她来的。
Look, she's waking up.
看，她醒了。
What's going on, Ellen?
怎么了，艾伦？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
The cat's out of the bag, you witch.
真相大白了，你这个女巫。
You can stop pretending now.
你现在可以停止假装了。
Yeah, Lois.
是啊，洛伊斯。
We know who you are.
我们知道你是谁。
Now we want some answers.
现在我们要一些答案。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这里？
You don't know who you're dealing with.
你不知道你在跟谁打交道。
You can't stop me.
你阻止不了我。
Run!
快跑！
Okay so what do you think will happen in part five?
好的，你们觉得第五部分会发生什么？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
Well what do you guys think will happen in part five?
那你们觉得第五部分会发生什么？
Actually Armand isn't a vampire anymore.
实际上阿曼德不再是吸血鬼了。
But Lois is a witch.
但洛伊斯是个女巫。
Who's Ellen?
艾伦是谁？
What sort of twist are we going to see here?
我们会看到什么样的转折？
Is she an alien?
她是外星人吗？
Oh my God.
哦，天哪。
We don't know what will happen but you can tell us what you think will happen.
我们不知道会发生什么，但你可以告诉我们你认为会发生什么。
Come to our website at EnglishPod.com and leave all your questions and comments and
来我们的网站 EnglishPod.com，留下你的所有问题和评论，
maybe your story ideas.
也许还有你的故事创意。
Yes, Marco and I are always around to answer your questions and to respond to your comments.
是的，马可和我随时都在回答你的问题并回复你的评论。
So guys, I think we're out of time for today but thanks for listening.
各位，我想我们今天时间到了，但感谢收听。
And we'll see you next time.
我们下次再见。
Goodbye.
再见。
Have a great week.
祝一周愉快。